Hello friends, Namaste, I am Singh and
once again a very welcome to our channel.
Friends, if you are also a
Common Service Center operator, that is, a
CSC center operator, then friends, this
video is going to be special for you
because friends, today we are going to talk about how
you can get
two-wheeler third party
insurance from ICICI Columba from your CSC center.
Friends, in this video we will tell you live
how you
can get third party insurance from ICICI Columba.
So friends, if you are on the channel for the
first time, then subscribe to the channel
and give the video a lovely like
because friends,
we keep bringing similar related videos for you from time
to time. So friends, let's
start the video. So friends,
first of all you have to login to the digital service portal. The
interface will open like this.
As you all must be knowing
how to login, after that,
friends, you will find an icon here which is for
insurance. So, you have to
click on it. As soon as you click, the
next page will open in front of you like this. Now, here
friends  If the interface opens like this, then
here you have to go to the last at the bottom,
here you get an option of
Motor Third Party, here friends you have to
click on Motor Third Party,
as if friends you will click here, then
a next interface will open like this,
now here friends
you will find many companies, whichever is
already connected with CSC, whichever
is connected with Common Service Center,
you will find all the insurance companies here,
so friends which company you
want to insure, friends
you will get all the companies here,
for that friends I will do it
from ICICI column bar here, so here
friends you have to enter ICICI here, that is,
you have to write
ICICI in this search bar and after writing it you will see
two options here,
here friends you see one option
of Motor Third Party POS and the second here
friends is Motor Third Party Wrap, so
here friends you have to click on this option, as soon as you click on the
wrap option, then the
next page will
open in front of you like this  There will be a little bit here, the
page which is loading will
open like this, now friends from here
you have to watch the video carefully and
understand well how to do
insurance, so for that here
friends you get an option of two wheeler,
here friends you have to do two wheeler i.e.
first party and here you
get an option of two wheeler TP third
party, so we will click on this,
after that here friends you will have a look
of renewal, so here friends
we do not have to do renewal and new, here we have to do
renewal, so here
we will click on the renewal option
and click on continue here,
after that the next page which will
come in front of us will redirect like this
and will open here like this,
now here friends what you have to do, the
dashboard has opened here, here
you have to fill all the details, whatever is there
in the RC, the registration number, you will fill it up here, that is,
after seeing the registration number in the RC, you will fill up the registration number here,
as soon as friends you
fill up the registration number, after that
Friends, here you get an option, Get
RTO Details. Here you get the option of Get RTO Details.
You must be seeing this way, you have to
click on this option.
As soon as you click on this option,
all the details will be displayed in front of you. The
date when your vehicle was registered will appear,
and friends, the RTO you belong to will
appear, and whatever state it is, it will appear here. In
this way, if it does
not appear here, then friends, you can enter it separately.
If it does not appear in the form, then
you can enter it separately. Everything has been entered
here, so
you will see everything here. Whatever is the model of your vehicle,
whatever it is, everything will be
automatically displayed here.
After that, you do not have to do anything here.
If you want a cover, you can do it, but
if you do not want to do anything here, you do not have to
click on Get Gate here.
After that, the next page will open like this.
Here, friends, you will see the view
premium, whatever amount you have to pay,
it will be shown here. It will be done
as here.  Friends, if it is 784, then
after that we will click on proceed here again.
As soon as we click on proceed,
then now you have to
fill up some further details here, as
friends, some details
are already filled up here, like friends, your engine number,
your chase number, whatever
details are there, they are already fetched here,
if friends, they are not fetched, then
you can enter them here, after that,
friends, if you want the cycle description, then you can
fill it up here, otherwise you
can leave it, after that, friends,
add nominee, which is the details, you have to
add a nominee here, then you
will click on the add nominee option here, if you want to
add other details here, then you
can do it, otherwise you can leave it, so
here you will click on the add nominee option, then
an option to add a nominee will open in front of you,
here
friends, you have to fill up the nominee name,
whatever is the name of the nominee, fill it up here,
after that
Friends, here you have to select the nominee relationship, that is, whatever is the relation of the nominee with the nominee, here you have to
select the relationship whether it is father, mother, father or friends, wife, husband, whatever it is.
After that, here you have to fill up the nominee age,
whatever is the age of the nominee,
you can also fill it up as per the Aadhar card. After that, create
new customer, that is, friends, now here you have to
fill up the customer's address, that is, name etc., so you have to select Mr., Mrs.,
whatever it is here.
After that,
you have to fill up the customer's name in the name option
here and after that,
after filling up the name here, you will see an option of date of birth here.
Friends, here you have to select the date
of birth from this calendar.
Whatever is the
date of birth of the customer, you have to select it here as per the
Aadhar card. After that,
friends, correspond here.  In address line
one, you have to fill up the address.
In line two also, you have to fill up the address.
You can put landmark in landmark,
otherwise you can also leave it. In pin code, you will
put the pin code, whatever area code
postal code it is. Select city here,
which is friends, in inter city, you have to
select the city, whatever it is.
After that, you have to select state here,
whatever is the state of the customer, you will
select it here and here friends, you have to
fill up the email ID and
fill up the mobile number here and here
friends, you have to fill up the PAN card number,
if there is, then you can fill it up, you can
also leave it otherwise. After that,
friends, here you have to click on generate proposal.
As friends, if you
click on this, then the next page will open in front of you like this.
Now friends,
here you get the proposal number, that is,
friends, in a way, you get the proposal number
here. Now
here friends, you do not have to do anything.
Here you have to click on the buy now option,
as friends, you buy
If you click on the Now option, friends, it will
take you directly to the CFC wallet
because you will now have to deduct the fee there.
So friends, we have come to our CFC wallet.
Here, friends, you have to
enter the password. Whatever your password is, you have to
enter your password here.
So friends, we fill up our password here.
You can also fill up your password in this way.
After filling up the password, friends, here you have to
click on the validate option.
After that, friends, you have to fill up your wallet PIN number
here. Whatever your
wallet PIN number is, you have to fill it up here.
After that,
you will click on the pay option here. As friends, if you
click on the pay option, the payment will
successfully pop up, that is, it will be done
directly. After that,
friends, here your policy will be completed and the fee will
also be paid. After that, friends, here
you get the policy number and the policy
start date is found here. You get the policy
end date.
You get to see everything here. After that,
friends, you will get to download the policy
here.  You have to click, like
friends, if you click on the download policy
option here, then your policy will be
downloaded, here you have to double
click and open the policy and
check it once, in this way
your policy will be downloaded here,
now friends you can print it out and
give it to the customer, your policy
is ready, friends, in this way you will be able to make
a policy very easily from your CSC portal,
whether you want to do it for third party
or first party or for a
motorcycle or for a car, whatever you want to do,
friends,
you can do it very easily, friends, if you have any
kind of doubt, question or query, then you
can comment below,
friends, if you liked this information, then
you must like it and we will meet again
in the next video of this type, till then
Jai Hind Jai Bharat